(忆往昔)
什么样的怪物会喜欢处女和金子
What kind of thing likes virgins and gold.
龙
Dragons.
是龙
Dragons,dude.
不要
No.
我就是觉得 最好
I just think it's better if.
慢慢来
You took it easy,you know.
别像是
And didn't act like you were.
被天使附身了一样
Possessed by an angel.
我想你认识Mills警长
I believe you know Sheriff Mills.
那不是我儿子
That was not my son.
- 你说得对 - 不
- You're right - No.
怎么干掉他们
How do we put them down.
今晚我们喝点什么
What're we drinking.
你们有不到一分钟时间
You have less than one minutes.
不然你们可爱的朋友就要窒息而死了
Before the very dear friend of yours snuff it.
停手吧 Crowley
Call it off,Crowley.
我看见你崩溃后的样子 Crowley
I saw you break down,Crowley.
我治愈你的过程中 我知道
When I was trying to cure you,I know.
你内心的一部分仍旧有人性
A part of you was human again,maybe.
- 也许现在还存在 - 废话连篇
- Still does exist - Blabla boohoo
(南达科他 哈特福德)
晚安 Slim
Nighty-night,Slim.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey - Hey.
- 你还好吗 - 嗯
- You okay - Yeah.
还好
Yeah.
就是
Just.
稍微休息了一下
Resting my head for a second.
Kevin怎么样
How's Kevin.
他
He.
他有什么新发现吗
He find anything.
没有
Jack.
已经4天了 连续没睡
On about four days,no sleep.
他看起来比你脸色都差
He looks worse than you.
Crowley呢
What about Crowley.
你觉得 他有没有可能
Do you think he might be lying about the whole.
在Metatron咒语不可逆这件事上说谎了
Metatron-spell-being-irreversible-thing.
那不是Crowley专长吗
What?Crowley?Lie.
不过我知道
I do know one thing.
下次那老混蛋再对人血上瘾
Next time that junkie's jonesing for a hit of blood.
我们手里有筹码
We got leverage.
说真的 你要个枕头吗
Seriously,you wanna a pillow.
不用 我没事
No,I'm fine.
- 你病了 - 我没病
- You're sick - No,I'm not sick.
我就是
I just.
怎么睡都睡不够的感觉
I fell like my battery can't recharge.
喂
Hello.
嘿 Dean 我是Jody Mills
Hey,Dean,Jody Mills.
Mills警长
Sheriff Mills.
等一下 Sam也在
Hang on.Sam's here too.
- 嗨Jody - 嗨Sam
- Hi,Jody - Hey,Sam.
我这儿有个反常的情况
I got a bit of an oddball to pitch your direction.
请说
Shoot.
我管辖的一个小镇子 就在苏福尔斯城外
Small town I cover outside the Sioux Falls.
开始只是失踪了几头牛
Only current speak of being occasional cow tipping.
但就在上周
Then last week.
有4人失踪
Four people go missing.
好吧 为什么觉得
All right,so what makes you think.
是我们管的事
That is our king of weird.
有个目击证人 说他昨晚看见
I got witness who says he saw someone.
有人拎起一辆车 抓走了一个女孩
Lift an SUV to nab a girl last night.
警长
Sheriff.
没再乱相亲什么的吧
Laying off the blind dates I hope.
你别哪壶不开提哪壶 小子
Yeah,you bite your tongue,boy.
嘿
Hey.
- 所以呢 - 是这样的
- So - So.
车就在那边
Car was right over there.
完全没有头绪
Ass over a teakettle.
通常 如果有人告诉我他看见
Now,normally,somebody tell me that one guy.
一个人拎起一辆车 我会直接把他打发走
Lift an SUV,I'd tell him to take a flying leap,but.
但在我那些所见所闻之后
After what I've seen.
没有什么是不可能的
Nothing's impossible.
这起事故怎么跟以前的失踪联系起来的
And this matches up the other missing how.
四起绑架 每起绑架的现场都有证据留下
Well,four abductions,strong evidence left every scene.
字面意义上的
Literally.
第一个受害人是一位牧师
So first vic was a pastor.
对
Yeah.
他书房的门被撞碎了
Door of his study was punched in.
然后是
And the next two.
一对订了婚的
Engaged couple.
上锁的窗户被大力扯开
Locked bedroom window was ripped open.
之后是这个女服务员
Then we have our waitress here.
和一辆被粗暴对待的车
With the topsy-turvy ride.
受害人之间有什么联系吗
Any other connection among them.
有
Yeah.
他们都是Good Faith教堂的成员
They are all members of Good Faith Church here.
我
My.
我在苏福尔斯城参加的
My church group back.
那个教堂对此很焦虑
In Sioux Falls was in a tizzy over it.
怎么了
What.
我以为你不是会去教堂的那种人
I didn't peg you for churchy.
是啊 你也知道
Yeah,you know.
被巫术害到差点在女卫生间的地上窒息
Chocked on the lady's room floor because of witchcraft.
相较之下 这种东西还是挺可靠的
Kinda makes a higher power seem relevent.
Jody 你确定
Jody,you sure you are.
你准备好回来工作了吗
Ready to jump back in the fray.
这种破事儿总是找上门
This wackadoo stuff keeps coming.
我知道得越多 就越有心理准备
More I know,better armed I'll be.
好吧 现在情况是
Okay,so,we have.
4个教堂成员失踪 还有超能力
Missing church folk and super strength.
也许是天使在找肉身
Maybe angels harvesting vessels.
可能又是个Boyle兄弟携手走光明事件
Can be a Buddy Boyle type thing.
等下 你们说天使
Wait,what,angels.
开玩笑地吧
You're joking.
非常严肃认真的说
Don't get your pants on fire.
他们是一群混蛋
They suck.
你说有目击证人
You said there was a witness.
对 算是吧
Yeah,well,more or less.
Slim
Okay,Slim.
我的两个朋友想跟你说说那个失踪女孩儿的事
My friends here wanna talk you about the missing girl.
Honor
Honor.
她叫Honor
Her name was Honor.
人很好
Nice girl.
总是给我留一口饭
Always left me meals.
Slim 说说昨晚的事
Slim,why don't you tell us what you saw last night.
我听到声响
Heard big noise.
就醒了
Got woke.
发现远处站了一人
And there somebody over there.
拎起一辆车
Lifting a car up.
像这样
Like this.
你看到是谁了吗
Did you happen to see who it was.
太远了
I was too far.
但是我看到有光
But I saw a light go off.
白光吗
A white light.
蓝光
Blue.
蓝色的火光
Blue light fire.
但不是
But not.
然后她就
And she was.
她就不见了
She wasn't there.
还有别的吗
Could you think of anything else.
没了
No.
嗯 好吧
Okay,well.
Slim 谢谢
Slim,thank you.
你能来
For your time.
好吧 没白光
Okay,so,no white light.
不是天使
No angel.
跟受害者的家属谈过吗
Has anybody talked to the vitims's families.
我正要去
It's next on my list.
你说他们都是
Okay,so you said they were.
一个教堂的对吧
All part of the same church.
准备好去做礼拜了吗
Ready to get your worship on.
希望你们能喜欢教堂介绍游
I hope you enjoy the tour.
注册之前 还有什么问题吗
Any questions before I get you boys registered.
有 是这样的
Yeah,look.
Futchko小姐
Miss Futchko.
别这样叫我
Oh,please.
叫我Bonnie就好
Bonnie will do just fine.
Bonnie 好
Bonnie,okay.
我们很喜欢这所教堂 真的
We,love the church.We do.
但是
But.
我们听说
What we heard that.
有几个成员失踪了
A few members have gone missing and.
说实话
To be honest.
我们有些被吓到了
It kinda scares us.
我跟你们保证
Let me assure you.
在我们安全防护措施下
With our increase security.
Good Faith是最安全的
Good Faith has never been safer.
那些失踪的人
And those people who've gone missing.
我们日夜为他们祈祷
Well,they are front and center in our preyers.
真是宽心不少
What a relief.
那你一定
Now,you must've been.
和她们关系很近吧
Close to them.
我们确实都是APU的
Well,you do share the APU bond.
- 什么APU - 我们的守贞小组
- The APU? - Our chastity group.
拒绝婚前性行为净化我们的身心
Abstinence Purify's Us.
哦
Oh.
我们可以去旁听一下吗
You mind if we sit it on that.
看看我们是否适合加入
Maybe see if it's for us.
很抱歉 这是会员制的
I'm afraid it's members only.
我真的很抱歉
I'm sorry but.
有时候的讨论 真的很私密
It can get...pretty personal.
那我们报名
Then count us in.
那么
Well.
我真是万分荣幸呢
I'll be a squirrel in a skirt.
我去拿入会表格 马上回来
I'll be back with in a jiff with the pappers.
- 你抽什么风 - Dean听我说
- A chastity group - Dean,listen.
如果所有失踪的人都是APU成员
If all the members are APU.
抓他们的怪物说不定在抓处子
Then maybe whatever took them is stocking virgins.
那个Slim 以为他看到了火
That Slim guys,thought he saw a fire.
你怎么看 龙吗
So,what do you think?Dragons.
好的
All righty.
签了字
Just sign there and.
你们的净化之旅就可以开始了
Your purification can begin.
守贞宣言
Purity pledge.
就是声明你是处子
It's a commitment to your virginity.
我觉得 这个貌似已经回不去了
I don't think we can really unring that bell.
你懂我意思
You know what I mean.
哦
Oh.
我知道了
I see.
这么说吧
Well.
如果你们请求上帝原谅你的罪
If you just ask for God's forgiveness for your sins.
并对你们的贞节守誓
And making you vow of your chastity.
你们在他眼里又会是处子一般
Well,then you'll be born again as a virgin in his eyes.
所以就是按一下
So,you just hit the virginity.
贞节重启键 然后他老人家就没问题了吗
Do over button and all's good with the man upstirs.
那不是一个按键
It's not a button.
还有
And.
这不仅是一张纸
This ain't just a piece of paper.
这是证明你们清白的凭证
I mean,this is your clean slate.
你们结婚前重守贞节的机会
Your chance to be a virgin until marriage.
既然你给了我洗白的机会
Well,you hand me a clean slate.
那还等什么
Let's do this.
恭喜你们 Sam Dean
Congratulations Sam and Dean Winchester.
你们又是处子了
You're both virgins.
求你了
Please.
别过来
Stay away from me.
下午好
Good afternoon,everyone.
我是Suzy
I'm Suzy.
嗨 Suzy
Hi,Suzy.
我们可以先从
I thought we began.
一个祷告开始
With a silent prayer.
阿门
Amen.
现在
Now.
有人想
Does anyone have anything that.
- 先开个头吗 - 我写了
- They would love to share - I wrote.
写了一篇诗 叫
A piece of verse.It's called.
性爱是罪恶地
Sex is racket.
上帝正看着你做出的每一个决定
And God's ball is in your court.
Timmy 我们真的很想听
We would love to here that,Timmy.
过会儿好吗
Later.
要不先从新朋友开始
Why don't we hear from our new friends.
Sam
Sam.
你为什么会来宣誓你的贞节
What brought you here to reclaim your virginity.
可能是因为跟我一起
Well,guess because I've been women I.
一起谈过恋爱的女生
I ever,had relations with.
最后结果都不怎么好
It hasn't ended well.
他没说谎
He ain't lying.
感谢你能来Sam
Thank you for being here,Sam.
亦坚强 亦守誓
Stay strong,stay pure.
你呢 Dean
And you,Dean.
你为什么想远离这种罪恶
What's that you wanna pass away from sin.
其实很难说具体为什么
Hard to say,exactly,you know.
做爱让人感觉 我说不来
Sex is always felt...I don't know.
感觉很好
Good.
非常 非常好
You know,really,really good.
但是
But.
有的时候又让你感觉很不好
Sometimes it just makes you feel bad.
比如 醉酒之后的一夜情
You know,you're drunk,you shack up.
一觉醒来之后的那点儿破事儿
Then it's the whole morning thing,you know.
嘿 昨天你真是太棒了
Hey that was fun.
然后就
And then.
好聚好散
Adios.
总是好聚好散
Always the adios.
但是真正做爱的时候 谁管得了那么多呢
You know when you get down to it,what's the big deal.
对吧 摸都摸了
Right?I mean,sure there's the touching.
感受着彼此全身的温度
And the feeling all of each other.
我的双手在她全身游走
My hands everywhere.
爱抚过每一寸肌肤
Tracing every inch of her body.
两个人一个节奏
The two of us moving together.
贴近 推开 厮磨
Pressing,pulling,grinding.
当你击中了那甜蜜的一点
Then you hit that sweet spot.
一切都变得微妙起来
Then everything just builds.
快感一波波冲刷过你的神经直到
And builds and builds until it all just.
没错
Yeah.
但是整个过程总是会有点儿
But the whole thing was just a little too.
黏黏的
Sticky.
所以
So.
我终于又是处了
I got my V-card back.
哈哈
The end.
所以
So.
你不觉得你话说太多了吗 Dean
Wee bit of overshare,Dean.
我是在净化我自己
I was purifying.
有没有觉得她很眼熟
Hey,she look familiar to you.
Suzy吗
Suzy.
嗯 我发誓我绝对在哪儿见过她
Yeah,swear I know her from somewhere.
嗯对啊 Dean
Oh,good Dean.
这理由永远都不会过时
That line never fails.
去看看
Let's find out.
- 嘿 - 所以呢
- Hey - So.
所以
So.
你喜欢今天的小会吗
How did you like the meeting.
哦 我 呃 呃 我很喜欢
Oh I...I...I loved it.
但是 我总是忍不住想
Yeah,you know,I couldn't help think of.
那些没来的人
Those who won't here.
Honor
Honor.
她是我最喜欢的姑娘
She's my favourite.
稍等我一下可以吗
Will you excuse you.
她最喜欢的吗
Her favourite.
她完全不知道
She has no idea.
Honor是什么样的人
What kind of girl Honor is.
这样啊
You don't say.
你叫Timmy对吧 写诗的那个
Timmy,right?the poet.
Timmy 要不
Timmy,why don't.
要不你跟我说说Honor是什么样的人
Why don't you tell me what kind of girl Honor is.
你确定我们不认识吗
Are you sure we don't know each other.
是 我确定我们从来没见过 Dean
Yeah,I'm pretty sure we've never met Dean.
等等 你是新来的对吧
Wait,you're new in town right.
对 环境对我来说是新的 守贞小组也是
Yeah,new to town,new to this whole chastity thing.
我还提供个人咨询
Well,I provide individual counselling.
如果你想说说话什么的
If you ever need to talk.
所以这儿的所有人都找你侃大山是吗
So everybody in the group,they dish to you.
是吐露心声
They confined.
拒绝婚前性行为如果没有支持
Abstinence is really rough without.
真的很难坚持下去
Support,education.
哦对了
Hey,you know what.
我有一些特别有益的书
I have some great books on the vowl.
对我帮助很大
That really help me.
我就住在附近 我去拿给你
I live close.I 'll just go grab one.
绑架案还没破
The kidnapper on the loose.
- 没事 - 这样吧
- I'll be fine - Tell you what.
我跟你一起去
Why don't I walk with you.
只是以防万一 好吗
Just to be safe,okay.
我马上就回来
Just give me one second.
糕点义卖活动我带来的可都是自己做的小饼干
And I bake real cookies for the bake sale.
Honor只带了奥利奥
Honor's just bring oreos.
抱歉 失陪一下
Well,you know,excuse me.
猜猜谁要跟老师一起回家
Guess who's taking the teacher home.
做调查哦
Research.
你真觉得你能拿下那个女人
You really think you're gonna hit that.
Dean 她是守贞小组的指导员
Dean,she's the chastity counselor.
没错 我知道
Yeah,I know.
你呢 运气如何
What about you,any luck.
如果你是问 我有没有认真工作
You mean,if I'm actually working.
我当然有在人人工作
As a matter of fact,yes,I am.
好吧 祝你好运
All right,well good luck with that.
好了 带路吧
Okay,make the way.
好呀
Okay.
嘿
Hey.
抱歉
Sorry,that.
咱们聊到哪儿了
So where were we.
Honor要下地狱了
Honor is going to hell.
嘿
Hey.
教堂怎么样
How was church.
结果一目了然
Well,it turned out to confessional,apparently.
其中两个受害者
Two our vics.
Honor和Fred牧师
Honor and Pastor Fred.
都破了禁
Did the dirty.
看起来他们不是唯一破禁的人
Oh,well,they're not the only ones.
Barb Blanten
Barb Blanten.
那位失踪的准新娘
Our missing bride-to-be.
怎么
Yeah.
她妈妈说 她听见Barb和她的的未婚夫
Her mom said,she heard Barb and her fiance.
在Barb的房间里
In Barb's badroom.
继续
Going at it.
她说她听到了做爱的声音
She said she heard sex noises.
Barb的哭声
Then Barb crying.
然后Neil告诉Barb刚才那个不算数
Then Neil telling Barb it didn't count.
因为一共才做了不到30秒钟
Because it was under thirty seconds.
两个小时后
Then two hours later.
她听到了撞击声 然后看见门缝里透出了光
She heard a smash and saw flashlight under the door.
蓝色的光吗
Blue light.
我觉得不管这东西是什么
You know I'm thinking whatever this thing is.
它的目标肯定不是处子
It's not going after virgins.
也不是新生的处子
Even born-again virgins.
它抓的是打破了守身宣言的处子
Taking virgins who break their chastity vow.
所以肯定不是龙
So dragons are off the list.
龙
Is there dragons.
真的有这玩意儿吗
Those are a thing.
有
Yeah.
太多东西都是真的了
Too many things are things.
别太拘谨
Make yourself comfortable.
现在可不行 小破孩
Not now,kiddo.
我一直在想我的朋友
I can't stop thinking about my friends.
我好害怕
I'm so scared for them.
你能跟我一起祈祷吗 Dean
Will you pray with me,Dean.
没问题
Sure.
这是Dean的另一个备用电话
This is Dean's other other cell so.
你知道该怎么办
You must know what to do.
Dean
Dean.
拜托给我回个电话
Come on,call me.
作为一个得到新生的人来说
You know for being borned again today.
你看上去真是太糟了
You sure look like crap.
等等
Wait a second.
- 你有没有 - 新生
- Did you get - Born again.
对
Yeah.
Sam
Sam.
我不会随便承诺自己做不到的事儿
I don't make promises I can't keep.
只是
It's just.
我喜欢教会
I enjoy church.
我是说
I mean after.
在经历过Bobby之后
After Bobby.
还有Crowley
Crowley.
我需要找点儿精神上的寄托
Just I need something that makes sense to me.
可能就是一种慰藉吧
You know,comfort,I guess.
我们都向往这个
I guess we all are looking for that.
除了那些已经得到了的人
Except for those who got it.
得了吧
Come on.
你和Dean
You and Dean.
你们俩之间肯定有点儿什么 你不觉得吗
That's something special,don't you think.
好了
Okay.
不如
So why don't you.
你先自己看看这些 我要去
Breeze through these and I'm gonna head to the.
去一下卫生间
You know,girl's room.
当然
Yeah.
嗨 Dean
Hi,Dean.
Dean
Dean.
嘿 你在听吗
Hey you there.
色情小屋
Casa Erotica.
喂
Hello.
Dean
Dean.
Sammy
Sammy.
嘿
Hey.
出什么事儿了吗
What's going on.
我有了重大发现
I found something big.
我们也是
Yeah,so do we.
听着 不是龙干的
So get this,it's not a dragon.
Dean
Dean.
知道了
Copy that.
嘿
Hey.
或者我应该说
Or should I say.
哎嘿
Hola.
为什么
Why.
没什么 没什么
No reason,no reason.
你还好吗
Are you okay.
我吗
Me.
棒极了
Great.
为什么这么问
Why.
你看起来 我不知道
You seem...I don't know.
很紧张
Nervous.
紧张
我才不紧张 Carmelita
I'm not nervous.Carmelita.
你看过我的那些 作品了
So you've seen my work.
要是你想换一个顾问的话 我不会怪你的
So I don't blame you if you want to be assigned a new.
我很理解
Counselor I,I get it.
不
No.
不不不
No,no,no,you.
开什么玩笑 你简直就是
Are you kidding me,I mean you're.
你就是个传奇
You're frigging legend.
不
No.
我已经不是那个女孩了
I am not that girl anymore.
我搬到了这儿 改了我的名字
I moved here,I changed my name.
那个女孩实在是
That girl was.
太可怕了
Was horrible.
听着
Listen.
Suzy
Suzy.
我见过很多可怕的东西
I've seen a lot of aweful things.
噩梦一般的事物
Stuffs of nightmares,okay.
但你不同
But you.
你是我最美好的梦
You're the good dreams.
这儿的人都不知道吗
And nobody in Hartford knows.
难道让我说
Yeah,what am I supposed to say.
嘿 没错我就是那个艳星 咱们来祈祷吧
Oh,yeah,hey,it's me,a porn star,let's prey.
他们完全没有看到你的价值
Well,they do not appreciate you.
我是说
I mean.
你的那些本领
The things you can do.
跟玉米卷的那些镜头
The scene with the tacos.
是啊
Yeah.
我愿意为了接近你
It made me want to join a mariachi band.
加入墨西哥街头乐队
Just to be near you.
你现在已经很近了
Well,you are now.
是很近 我很近了对吧
I am,aren't I.
你不像
You're not like.
镇子里其他的男人
The other guys in town,are you.
你更像是个
You're kind of a.
坏男孩
A bad boy.
我不知道
I don't know.
为什么不试试用西班牙语问我
Why don't you ask me that in Spanish.
你是个坏男孩吗
Eres un chico malo.
没错
Si.
Fred神父
Pastor Fred.
Neil
Neil.
Barb
Barb.
怎么回事
What was that.
他怎么变成了这个样子
What happened to him.
你以为呢 他是饿死的
What do you think,he's starving to death.
要是我们不逃出去 也是一样的下场
Just like we will if we don't get out of here.
为什么不告诉我你们是谁
Why didn't you tell me who you were.
我快吓死了
I'm so scared.
我们也很害怕
We were scared.
他去哪儿了
Where did he go.
怎么了
What's up.
这个东西抓的都是违背守身宣言的人 对吧
This thing is taking people who breaks their vows,right.
没错
Yeah.
Dean和Suzy
Dean and Suzy.
已经出去了一个多小时了
Been over an hour.
对
Right.
不得不说
Gotta say.
我还挺怀念的
I really missed that.
我已经怀念很久了
I miss it already.
好吧
Okay.
你在干什么
What are you doing.
我好渴
I'm so thirsty.
好渴
So thirsty.
一定有出去的方法
It has to be a way out.
Dean 醒醒
Dean,hey come on.
Dean
Dean.
这是哪儿
Where are we.
地狱
Hell.
嘿
Hey.
邻居看见什么了吗
Neighbours see anything.
蓝光一闪而过
Flash blue.
你确定Dean来过这儿
You sure Dean was here.
非常确定
Oh,yeah.
而且 他成功实现计划了
And I think he crossed someone off his bucket list.
我们试过了
We tried.
根本没有出路
There's no escape.
咱们会缺氧至死吗
Are we gonna run out of air.
我不这么觉得
I don't think so.
有人想让咱们一点一点死去
Somebody wants us to die nice and slow.
我们死了以后都会被带走
And then it's gonna take us.
就像Fred牧师一样
Just like it took pastor Fred.
什么东西带走了他
What took him.
我们看不清
We couldn't see exactly.
那光实在是太刺眼了
It was so bright.
就像 就像是火光一样
It,it was like it was on fire.
嘿
Hey.
处子
Virgins.
火焰
Fire.
耳熟吗
Sound familiar.
Vesta 罗马女灶神
Vesta,Roman God of the hearth.
古罗马时期
Ancient Rome.
每年都要选出6个处子给这个妞儿当牛做马
6 virgins were dedicated to this chick every year.
他们的主要指责是照料Vesta的灶火
Their main duty was to tend Vesta's hearth.
等等
Wait so.
所以火焰跟童贞有关
Fire is connected to virginity.
是的
Yeah.
必须都是处女
The girls had to be pure because.
因为火是纯洁的象征
Fire is a symbol of purity.
只要灶火一直不熄灭
As long as the fire was kept to lit.
罗马就能迎来丰收
Roman recieved a good harvest.
被选出的处子必须守身30年
The virgins had to stay celibate for 30 years.
如果他们打破了誓言
If they broke their vows.
就会被活埋
They were burried alive.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
Dean
Dean.
这一切也许都是上帝的意志
Maybe God wants us down here.
因为我们刚那什么了
Because of what we did.
相信我 这可不是上帝干的事儿
Trust me this is not God's work.
它个混
Son of a.
怎么了
Why,what's wrong.
我手机没了
It took my phone.
很幸运
Luckily.
我还有一个
I keep a spare.
别掉链子啊
Come on,bars.
Vesta总是出现在一团蓝色的圣光里
Vesta was often enveloped in a blue halo of light.
她可以控制蓝光攻击人类
Which she could control it to disorient to maim.
也可以杀死
Or to kill.
有没有提到怎么杀死她
So what about some ways to kill her.
任何武器或者其他的
Weapon or something.
Dean
Dean.
Sam Sammy
Sam Sammy.
- Dean - 嘿 嘿 听我说 我在
- Dean - Hey,hey,listen to me,I'm.
- Dean - 我地下
- Dean - I'm underground.
- 再说一遍我听不清 - 我们在
- Say it again,I can't hear you - We're.
是
Some kind of.
Dean
Dean.
没信号了
Lost him.
什么
What.
等等 这附近有没有
Wait a sec,is there some kind of a.
火车站之类的地方
Train station around here or something.
我听到了汽笛声
I could have sworn I heard a whistle.
别 Neil 别这么干
Don't,Neil,please,don't.
别干什么 Neil
Don't what,Neil.
管好你自己的事儿就行了 老兄
Just mind your beeswax,pal.
听着
Listen.
我们们都被困在这下面
We're all stuck down here together.
你要有什么想说的
So you got something to say.
就直说
You say it.
好吧 不论那个火球到底是什么东西
Okay,look,whatever that fireball thing was.
它抓走了最虚弱的人
It's taking the weakest.
我不想做下一个
And I'm not gonna the next.
她的腿反正也已经不能用了
So the way I see it,her leg's busted anyway.
不如咱们分吃了她 还能争取点儿时间
We serve her up,it could buy us some time.
你去死吧 Neil
Screw you,Neil.
腿不能用
Busted leg.
只是脚扭伤了
Try a sprained ankle,okay.
没人能吃掉任何人
Nobody serve anybody up.
我们被恐慌包围着
We're under the gallows.
你我都是
All of us.
先从她下手
Give it Honor.
说不定能救了我们所有人
It might save the rest of our necks.
除非你有更好的主意
Unless you have a better plan.
或许我还真有
Maybe I do.
或许我们应该先把你交出去
Maybe we'll give him you.
什么 你不喜欢这个主意吗
Oh,what you don't like that idea.
那就给我闭嘴
Then shut up.
我查到了
Here we go.
一辆8点左右驶出苏福尔斯的火车
8 pm train out of a Sinoux Falls.
每小时79英里的速度
79 miles an hour.
哈特福德东边5英里是什么地方
What's five miles east of Hartford,anything.
应该都是草场
Pasture mostly.
不
No.
老Wimmer农场
The old Wimmer farm.
等一下 拿什么做武器
Wait,anything got a weapon.
沾有处子血的橡树枝
Oak,stained in virgin blood.
我们去哪找处子
Where are we gonna get a virgin.
我就是处子
I am a virgin.
我觉得我们需要的是真处子 Sam
I think we need the real McCoy here Sam.
你们需要什么
You need what.
你的血
Your blood.
就一点点
Just a dab.
邪教徒才会用血 你们是邪教徒吗
Pagans use blood.Are you pagans.
什么 邪教
What?Pagan.
不 是为了做一个武器
No,look it's for a weapon.
你们就在一个教堂里
You are in a House of God.
你们的邪恶仪式不可能在这里进行
Your psycho rituals aren't gonna fly here.
我们没时间跟你解释了
We don't have time for this.
我也没时间跟恶魔崇拜者废话
I don't have time for devil worshipers.
我要叫警察了
I'm calling the cops.
我就是警察
I'm the cops.
搞什么啊
What the fudge lady.
擦擦鼻子吧 亲爱的
Wipe your nose,dear.
你也破戒了
You broke too huh.
我想我没有自己想象中的那么坚强
Guess I'm not strong as I thought I was.
主原谅众生 你自己这么告诉我的
God forgives.You told me that yourself.
早给你说了 他回来抓人的
Told you,it's back for one of us.
你现在要怎么办
What are you gonna do now.
你应该听我的
Right you should have listened to me.
闭嘴 安静
Shhh!Shut up.
Jody
Jody.
Sam
Sam.
Dean 我们来了 马上救你们出来
Dean!We're here.We're gonna get you out.
Jody 我找到了
Jody I found it.
Sammy Sammy
Sammy Sammy.
Sammy
Sammy.
Dean 我们来了
Hey Dean we are here.
我们马上救你们出来
We're gonna get you out.
Sammy
Sammy.
你还在吗
Are you still there.
Sam
Sam.
好了好了 嘘
Now now,shhh.
真的吗 你们神就是这么办事儿的吗
Really,this is how Goddess acts.
什么
What.
我对这方面还不怎么在行 但是
I'm sort of new to this,but you know.
堂堂罗马神居然把人活埋在仓库里
A Roman deity burying people alive in a barn.
不觉得有点可悲么
Sort of pathetic don't you think.
只有在我开始一个人
It only got pathetic.
做这些的时候才是可悲
When I start having to do it myself.
要不是那个从伯利恒来的破烂货
Because of that hippie from Bethlehem.
他出现之前 都是我一人独享处子
Before him,they practically threw virgins at me.
然后现在
And now.
他们放任你的灶火不管 把你抛在了脑后
They let your fire go out and they forget about you.
是啊 我知道
Yeah,I know.
总是排在第二名做Lindsay Lohan
Sucks to be Lindsay Lohan.
可不好受 对吧
Doesn't it.
实际上
Actually.
我想通了 如果反抗不了
I figure it if you can't beat'em.
那就加入他们吧
Join them.
对啊 我学会了变通
That's right,I adapted.
现在我学会了祷告
Now I chew on the cud of prayer.
真见鬼
Heck.
我甚至有了这样的毛衣
I even got a sweater set.
有螺丝刀么
Screwdriver,anybody.
嘿
Hey.
急救箱里找到的
From the first-aid kit.
过去人们会争先恐后的为我守身如玉
They use to beg to stay pure for me.
现在 轮到我拖着她们
And now,I have to drag them.
挣扎着尖叫着
Kicking and screaming.
他们甚至不是真正的处子
And they're not even real virgins.
他们是新生的处子
They are born-again.
你还说我可悲
Talk about pathetic.
你就是个典型的阶下囚
Yeah,you are a charity case.
错了 我的小心肝 这可不是施舍
Oh no sweet heart.This isn't charity.
我只是拿了我该得的
I take what I deserve.
那些荡妇们葬身之时
When those trollops are about to die.
肉体浸染着鲜美的恐惧感
Soaked in their juicy fear.
我会吃掉她们的肝
I eat their livers.
因为这是她们身上唯一
Because that's the only part of them still working to.
还在起净化作用的部分
Purify the body that they've trashed.
我一般喜欢让猎物变得虚弱
Now normally I'd like them weaker.
但我得为猎人破个例 是不是
But let's just call this a hunter's exception shall we.
好啊
Sure.
这就是我们神的作风
This is how I goddess acts.
快点 快点
Come on come on.
你是怎么回事
What's wrong with you.
什么
What.
你的肝 都坏了
Your liver,it's no good.
天啊 你的身体已经从里面坏掉了
Dear boy,you're all duct tape and safety pins inside.
你怎么还能活着
How are you alive.
我错过了什么
What did I miss.
要走了吗
Heading out.
是啊 跟你们说过别到处惹麻烦 但是
Yeah,I tell you boys stay out of trouble but.
说了也没用
What's the point.
谢谢你救我出来
Thanks for bailing me out.
我能说什么好呢
What can I say.
我已经救顺手了
I'm getting the hang of this.
慢点开车
Drive safe.
谢了
Thanks.
不用给我开门什么的了
Don't get the door for me or anything.
怎么了
What's up.
如果我真的有什么问题怎么办
What if there is something wrong with me.
特别严重的问题
Something really wrong.
你只是累坏了 你需要休息
You just crapped out man.You need some rest.
不 比这更严重
No it's more than that.
Vesta说我只是行尸走肉
I mean Vesta said I was practically dead inside.
怎么 她现在是你的闺蜜了吗
Oh and she's in the circle of trust now.
她有必要说谎么
Why would she lie.
肯定是那些试炼
It's probably the trials.
好么 就像一种 后遗症
Ok?That was sort of...you know,after effect.
就像感冒之后的后遗症
It's like you're bouncing back of a flu here.
当时你全身都发着不正常的红光
I mean you were glowing with freaking trial juice.
我不知道
I don't know.
不然还能是什么
Well what else would it be.
为什么一定会有别的什么呢
Why does it have to be something else.
总是有别的东西不对
It's always something else.
我们总是绞尽脑汁想出一个其他解释
We're always scraping to find some other explanation.
有可能问题就是我自己
Well maybe it is just me.
不要这样Sam
Come on Sam.
我现在一团糟 Dean你也知道的
I'm a mess Dean and you know it.
有时候我就是觉得
Sometimes I feel like.
我可能永远都不会好了
Maybe I'll never ganna actually be alright.
你会好的
You will.
不管是什么问题我们都能解决
What ever it is we'll figure it out.
或许
Or this is.
我本来就这样
Just the way I am.
我做不到
I can't.
我没法让你继续这样下去了
I can't let you put this on yourself.
听着
Listen to me.
这不是真的你Sam
It's not you Sam.
要是我 就不会告诉他 Dean
I wouldn't do that,Dean.
他应该知道真相
He deserve to know.
你的弟弟还没准备好
Your brother is not ready.
如果他排斥我他肯定挺不过去
If he reject me he will not make it.
见鬼Zeke我们还要这样玩捉迷藏玩多久
Damn Zeke how much longer we have to keep playing this.
不会很久了 我向你保证
Not much longer I promise you that.
什么
What.
什么 什么不是我
What what's not me.
没什么 我是说
Nothing I just...I meant that.
如果有什么不对 也不是你的不对
If there is something wrong,it's not your fault.
我们会解决的
We'll deal with it.
你要有点信心Sammy
You've got to have a little faith Sammy